<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Irene&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Irene&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Music and Machine Learning Brainstorm</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/music-generation-brainstorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/music-generation-brainstorm/</guid>
      <description>My favorite hobbies revolve around music as I enjoy playing the piano, the flute, and dancing. Additionally, I enjoy building both tangible and virtual projects. In the future, I would like to major in Computer Science, and currently am most appealed in the field of machine learning. Thus, I would like to combine my interests to create a machine learning project that would benefit music education.
Below are some of my project brainstorm ideas as well as how they can fulfill the needs for people from a variety of backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Learning(2) - Hugo and Rebase</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/git-learning2-hugo-and-rebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/git-learning2-hugo-and-rebase/</guid>
      <description>What is Hugo? Hugo provides sample website templates, which include intructions in simple English language in how to fill in different sections. Once that is complete, Hugo will automatically generate the html code for the website using the template. The website can then be published using a url domain such as one from github.
How?** Once template has been filled out, the static page can be build using code below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Figure Reflection</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/hidden-figure-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/hidden-figure-reflection/</guid>
      <description>In the Declaration of Independence, Thomas Jefferson wrote that “All men are created equal”. However, history contradicts this as the fight for equality between genders and between races has not yet ended even as of now in the twenty-first century. Hidden Figures: The American Dream and the Untold Story of the Black Women Mathematicians Who Helped Win the Space Race by Margot Lee Shetterly was set in the 1960s, when the civil rights movement was prominent as people protested unfair laws and when the feminist movement had people fighting for greater personal freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Holiday</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/favorite-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/favorite-holiday/</guid>
      <description>My favorite holiday
Halloween
 U can reflect ur fav character With friendsm, school spirit Brother   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Learning(1) - Push</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/git-learning1-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/git-learning1-push/</guid>
      <description>What is Hugo? To push changes of website from .md to github through git First time:
1. git init 2. git add . 3. git status 4. git commit -m &amp;quot;first commit&amp;quot; 5. git branch -M main 6. git remote add origin https://github.com/ireneyrzd/Homepage.git 7. git push -u origin main After origin and main has been initialized:
1. git status 2. git add &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; 3. git rm &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; 4. git status 5.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
