<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Reflections on Irene&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/tags/personal-reflections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Reflections on Irene&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ireneyrzd.github.io/tags/personal-reflections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Figure Reflection</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/hidden-figure-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/hidden-figure-reflection/</guid>
      <description>In the Declaration of Independence, Thomas Jefferson wrote that “All men are created equal”. However, history contradicts this as the fight for equality between genders and between races has not yet ended even as of now in the twenty-first century. Hidden Figures: The American Dream and the Untold Story of the Black Women Mathematicians Who Helped Win the Space Race by Margot Lee Shetterly was set in the 1960s, when the civil rights movement was prominent as people protested unfair laws and when the feminist movement had people fighting for greater personal freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Holiday</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/favorite-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/favorite-holiday/</guid>
      <description>My favorite holiday is:
Halloween!!
 You can reflect on what was your favorite character in the past year Share bondings with friends as you discuss whether you want to make a group costume together and make plans for trick or treat A demonstration of school spirit during our annual parade showcaseing our costume around campus During October leading up to Halloween, can use the promise of taking him to trick-or-treat as a bribe to little brother for listening to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
