<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Reflections on Irene&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/tags/personal-reflections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Reflections on Irene&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ireneyrzd.github.io/tags/personal-reflections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Figure Reflection</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/hidden-figure-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/hidden-figure-reflection/</guid>
      <description>The novel, Hidden Figures: The American Dream and the Untold Story of the Black Women Mathematicians Who Helped Win the Space Race by Margot Lee Shetterly, particularily captured my attention when I saw the title. In middle school, I had watched a film about how these African American women were the brain and computers behind the construction of NASA’s spacecrafts. It really captivated me how during WWII, a time of bloodshed and violence, they were able to use their mathematical skills and intelligence, to make one calculation at a time, though seemingly small, but combined, they made a significant progress in America’s discovery of outerspace, gender, and racial equality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Holiday</title>
      <link>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/favorite-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ireneyrzd.github.io/post/favorite-holiday/</guid>
      <description>My favorite holiday is:
Halloween!!
 You can reflect on what was your favorite character in the past year Share bondings with friends as you discuss whether you want to make a group costume together and make plans for trick or treat A demonstration of school spirit during our annual parade showcasing our costume around campus During October leading up to Halloween, I can use the promise of taking him trick-or-treating as a bribe to my little brother to listen to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
